nakedsword.com 2006-11-20

# NakedSword's Privacy Policy :: NAKEDSWORD *turbo*

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our every page of our site. 

**The Information We Collect:**   
When you sign up with our billing provider, we are given your email address, subscriptionID and transactionID. Please see our authorized merchant's Privacy Policy concerning collected information from them. When you fill out a trouble report form, we ask you to submit information about your computer, connection and software. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the NakedSword website. 

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information that we get from our billing provider to verify that you have purchased a membership. Additionally, we use your email address to give you access to NakedSword and its services. Any information submitted to us on our trouble report form is only used to help us diagnose your specific problem(s). 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing [support@nakedsword.com](mailto:support@nakedsword.com). Please include your user name and password and use "Please Send Personal Information" in the subject line of your email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800.419.9287 or send us an email at [support@nakedsword.com](mailto:support@nakedsword.com).
